Hello friends, welcome to you all
once again
and we have to make a claim for it now, so
in that condition,
how will we add the name of the new insurance company in our DMS, that is, if it is
called total, then
before making the estimate, it is important for us to see in
which company's name we are
making the estimate, so friends, for this,
first of all, I will log in to my v20 ID
and after that,
I have made a job card for accidental,
I will open that job card and show it to you,
along with that, I will go to its estimate and
show you whether the company from which I
want to make the estimate is there or
not, so what will I do from here,
I will copy the job card number, here
I went to job card and
after that from here I
click on accidental job card,
so I click on this accidental job card, then
here you can see that
currently two accidental job
cards are open in my DMS, so here I will copy the card of any one job
Let me copy it.
After copying it, I will go to the service request and then
after entering the job card number,
I will press enter.
After clicking on this title that opens,
I will again click on the job card number here.
After scrolling down a bit, I will
click on the estimate button here. You
can see that the name of the insurance company is there here
and as soon as you click on this search box,
you will see the name of that company.
You have just insured the company
and the
name of the company for which you are making the estimate is visible here. So
you can see that right now there are names of two insurance companies in my DMS
and suppose I do not have to make a claim from A B and both of them, right
now I have to make a claim from some C
company, so in that condition now
I need to add a new name here.
You can see friends, right now
only two insurance company
names are added in my DMS and I have to prepare the estimate of some third company right now.
So
what will I do for this, first of all
I will click on the master button in the first level view bar and here
you can see the second level view bar  There is an
option of insurance company, if
I click there, here I will have the
same two options A B C D sorry AB, the
company whose name I showed you while I was making the estimate.
Now here I have to
add the name of a third company, so
what I will do is there is a new button here, I will
click on the new button and after that
you will have to enter the bank name, which
insurance company or bank's
name you want to add here, so I
want to add the name of some X company here, so I will write the name of that X company
here, then after that here the
mobile number and GST number, so step by
step I fill up the required details here, the
registered type is here, so you will enter it here, you will be
asked for the registered type, after that
you will enter the GST number here, so if
you do not know the GST number, then you
can contact the concerned insurance company or you can ask their
supervisor or executive
and here you will
fill up its GST number here, so what
I have done here is  GST number is there
and I have almost filled it up. After this,
friend, you need to fill up a little more details below,
like here it is
asking for its address etc., all are categories,
so to fill up the address here, I will
click on the address and press new here,
like I will press new here, in
this window that opens here, you will enter your state as per your choice,
which state you are from
and the address of the insurance company, you will
fill in the address of the insurance company here, friends, you will
not press your name, sorry, so here,
suppose the insurance company's head office is in your district
or in your state, you will
fill up the address in its name, so
here I will fill up the address in the name of my district
because
its main branch is in my district,
so let me fill up
its district, taluka, everything here. After this,
its pin code number is being asked below,
I will also enter the pin code number here,
like I entered the pin code number, after that
what will I do here, i.e., what is
its distance from my workshop in kilometers,
after entering it, I will press save.  I
will click on the button, it gets saved and
with the drop button you will press the OK button.
Now here you will put all the categories like service
parts or sales, whatever you need,
so I have put service here.
After filling up all the details,
friends, what will you do, as soon as you control yourself, this
data gets saved
in our DMS or if you click
anywhere outside in this screen once,
it also gets saved. There is
no need to control yourself. Now I will
again go to the same job card, the same estimate and show
you. I just
showed you that in my DMS, the
names of two companies were visible. Now you can see that there are
three companies here. I have just added one company.
In the beginning of the video, I had shown you
friends that there are two companies A and B here.
Now if I want to add any company C, then
how to add it, I had
shown you in the beginning itself. Now in this way,
friends, I have added the name of any insurance company
in my Row DMS i.e. Row Connect ID.  The
process was shown to you,
friends, how did you like the video, please do
tell us by commenting and if you found this video even a little
helpful, then like the video
and do not forget to subscribe to the channel, we will
meet friends in another new
explosive video, till then do
not forget to watch our old videos.